Guide to the Vassar College Alumnae/i Biographical Files (AAVC), circa 1865-2015
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- 1915
  - Fuller, M Winifred (Box 42)
  - Gardner, Clara J (Box 42)
  - Gifford, Helen W. (Box 42)
  - Glen, Ethel M. (Box 42)
  - Glenn, Elizabeth (Box 42)
  - Goh, Nabe (Box 42)
  - Gordy, Lucia H. (Box 42)
  - Gray, Flora A. (Box 42)
  - Grow, Helen (Box 42)
  - Gurney, Vivian (Box 42)
  - Hackney, Katharine (Box 42)
  - Haff, Madeline B. (Box 42)
  - Hagar, Gertrude S. (Box 42)
  - Haigh, Susanna E. (Box 42)
  - Hamilton, Florence N. (Box 42)
  - Hamilton, Ruth (Box 42)
  - Hamlin, C Louise (Box 42)
  - Hartmann, Helen (Box 42)
  - Hasbrouck, Ellen B. (Box 42)
  - Hass, Alma M. (Box 42)
  - Hazen, Dorothy (Box 42)
  - Heilman, Helen E. (Box 42)
  - Heimberger, Lucile O. (Box 42)
  - Heinsheimer, Stella (Box 42)
  - Helmer, May (Box 42)
  - Hendrick, Ruth Elisabeth (Box 42)
  - Herring, Elizabeth B. (Box 42)
  - Hipple, Charlotte A. (Box 42)
  - Holt, Dorothy E. (Box 42)
  - Hooker, Ambolena H. (Box 42)
  - Hopper, Ruth J (Box 42)
  - Horney, Grace (Box 42)
  - Hotchkiss, Margaret (Box 42)
  - Howard, Clara H. (Box 42)
  - Howard, Gladys W. (Box 42)
  - Howard, Grace E. (Box 42)
  - Howard, Margaret L. (Box 42)
  - Howe, Josephine R. (Box 43)
  - Howell, Hazel H. (Box 43)
  - Hubbard, Lois D. (Box 43)
  - Hyman, Dorothy B. (Box 43)
  - Ives, Martha L. (Box 43)
  - Jessup, Theodosia D. (Box 43)
  - Johnson, Eleanor R. (Box 43)
  - Johnson, Mary E. (Box 43)
  - Jones, Jeannette E. (Box 43)
  - Kaufmann, Hermine B. (Box 43)
  - Keith, Barbara (Box 43)
  - Kendig, Marjorie Mercer (Box 43)
  - Keniston, Mildred R. (Box 43)
  - Kennedy, A Beatrice (Box 43)
  - Kennedy, Anna Clark (Box 43)
  - Kinsey, Helen (Box 43)
  - Kinsey, Imogen (Box 43)
  - Klein, Esther L. (Box 43)
  - Kneeland, Natalie (Box 43)
  - Koster, Mathilde A. (Box 43)
  - Kush, Alice (Box 43)
  - Lammert, Olive M. (Box 43)
  - Lapham, M Diantha (Box 43)
  - Leech, Margaret K. (Box 43)
  - Lemon, Mary M. (Box 43)
  - Lesher, Theresa (Box 43)
  - Lester, Emma P. (Box 43)
  - Lloyd, Helen (Box 43)
  - Locke, Hannah S. (Box 43)
  - Lockwood, Cordelia A. (Box 43)
  - Lockwood, Ruth G. (Box 43)
  - Lovell, Margaret L. (Box 43)
  - Macintyre, Mona V. (Box 43)
  - Mallon, Mary (Box 43)
  - Maltby, Elizabeth M. (Box 43)
  - Manross, Martha D. (Box 43)
  - Marburg, Frances T. (Box 43)
  - Marjarum, Mildred H. (Box 43)
  - Marvin, Kathryn T. (Box 43)
  - Mason, Blanche L. (Box 43)
  - Mattice, Marion B. (Box 43)
  - May, Marjorie F. (Box 43)
  - McAfee, Ruth (Box 43)
  - McCormick, M Grace (Box 43)
  - McMullen, Katherine W. (Box 43)
  - Means, Glenn (Box 43)
  - Merriman, Faith (Box 43)
  - Metzger, Ruth I. (Box 43)
  - Miller, Dorothy C. (Box 43)
  - Miller, V Isabelle (Box 43)
  - Miller, Muriel (Box 43)
  - Moore, Nancy C. (Box 43)
  - Mordorf, Jeanne R. (Box 43)
  - Morrison, Frances J (Box 43)
  - Muhlfelder, Elsa (Box 43)
  - Murdock, Florence L. (Box 43)
  - Nash, Ruth S. (Box 43)
  - Nesmith, H Louise (Box 43)
  - Nicholls, Elizabeth G. (Box 43)
  - Nichols, Gertrude H. (Box 43)
  - Norton, Ruth W. (Box 43)
  - Ogden, Frances P. (Box 43)
  - Oldenburg, Margaret E. (Box 43)
  - Oliver, Katharine S. (Box 43)
  - O’neil, Teresa G. (Box 43)
  - Owens, Theodora L. (Box 43)
  - Parsons, Harriet M. (Box 43)
  - Patrick, M Dinsmore (Box 43)
  - Peirce, Katharine E. (Box 43)
  - Penniman, Rachel B. (Box 43)
  - Peterson, Marion (Box 43)
  - Petterson, Julia C. (Box 43)
  - Pierce, Frances (Box 43)
  - Polk, Mary M. (Box 43)
  - Pound, Mary W. (Box 43)
  - Pratt, Marjorie F. (Box 43)
  - Prescott, Helen (Box 43)
  - Prince, Ethel A. (Box 43)
  - Pritchard, Helen B. (Box 43)
  - Pursley, Ruth E. (Box 43)
  - Pyle, Ella Wise (Box 43)
  - Rabell, Susie B. (Box 43)
  - Raylea, Clutha E. (Box 43)
  - Reed, Leslie Palmer (Box 43)
  - Reynolds, Martha May (Box 43)
  - Rhodes, Catharine I. (Box 43)
  - Rice, Dorothy L. (Box 43)
  - Richardson, Portia (Box 43)
  - Ringwood, Irene C. (Box 43)
  - Ringwood, Vera X (Box 43)
  - Robinson, Catharine D. (Box 43)
  - Ross, Mary E. (Box 43)
  - Ruef, Bertha M. (Box 43)
  - Rumsey, Jean H. (Box 43)
  - Russell, Alice E. (Box 43)
  - Sanborn, Aenid A. (Box 43)
  - Sanborn, Helen M. (Box 43)
  - Sasse, Alma B. (Box 43)
  - Schwoerer, Frances May (Box 43)
  - Scott, Margaret (Box 43)
  - Seaman, Louise H. (Box 43)
  - Seymour, Laura S. (Box 43)
  - Shapard, Elizabeth (Box 43)
  - Shapley, Bertha (Box 43)
  - Sheperd, Miriam G. (Box 44)
  - Sherwood, Helen L. (Box 44)
  - Skinner, Frances L. (Box 44)
  - Smith, Flora M. (Box 44)
  - Smith, Lucia H. (Box 44)
  - Smith, Ruth E. (Box 44)
  - Spalding, Gertrude A. (Box 44)
  - Spratt, Marjorie K. (Box 44)
  - Stanley-Brown, Ruth (Box 44)
  - Stanwood, Ruth (Box 44)
  - Stebbins, Blanche (Box 44)
  - Stewart, Marjorie M. (Box 44)
  - Stokes, Eleanor (Box 44)
  - Stone, Helen W. (Box 44)
  - Strait, Helen F. (Box 44)
  - Strayer, Maude-Louise (Box 44)
  - Sutherland, Natalie (Box 44)
  - Sutton, Doris M. (Box 44)
  - Sutton, Mildred (Box 44)
  - Taft, Marjorie E. (Box 44)
  - Talmadge, Fanny E. (Box 44)
  - Taylor, Margaret (Box 44)
  - Taylor, Martha E. (Box 44)
  - Thrasher, Ruth (Box 44)
  - Tolhurst, Hope (Box 44)
  - Tomkins, Jeannette (Box 44)
  - Topping, Gladys M. (Box 44)
  - Tryon, Sylvia (Box 44)
  - Tweedy, Margery B. (Box 44)
  - Upson, Helen (Box 44)
  - Upson, Lucile (Box 44)
  - Van Brunt, Elizabeth R. (Box 44)
  - Van Hoesen, Enid (Box 44)
  - Van Zandt, Marjorie (Box 44)
  - Verity, Hilda (Box 44)
  - Viquesney, Bernice (Box 44)
  - Wagner, Margaret E. (Box 44)
  - Walworth, Lillian (Box 44)
  - Ward, Harriot S. (Box 44)
  - Ward, Laura A. (Box 44)
  - Wedge, Ruth P. (Box 44)
  - Weil, Elise (Box 44)
  - Weiss, M Therese (Box 44)
  - Welles, Katharine R. (Box 44)
  - Wells, Katherine Z. (Box 44)
  - West, Helen C. (Box 44)
  - Weyerhaeuser, Elizabeth L. (Box 44)
  - Wheeler, Ellen R. (Box 44)
  - Wheeler, Grace L. (Box 44)
  - Whish, Mary- Elizabeth (Box 44)
  - White, Charlotte L. (Box 44)
  - White, Karin A. (Box 44)
  - White, Sophie D. (Box 44)
  - Wilbur, Ethel H. (Box 44)
  - Williams, Beatrice H. (Box 44)
  - Wilson, Rose D. (Box 44)
  - Witter, Grace B. (Box 44)
  - Wood, Gladys J (Box 44)
  - Wood, Mary C. (Box 44)
  - Woodruff, Gertrude (Box 44)
  - Woodward, Anna M. (Box 44)
  - Workum, Pauline M. (Box 44)
- 1916
  - Allen, Mildred F. (Box 44)
  - Allen, Mildred (Box 44)
  - Andrews, Constance M. (Box 44)
  - Anthony, Marjorie P. (Box 44)
  - Armstrong, Martha G. (Box 44)
  - Arnold, Marjorie (Box 44)
  - Arthurs, Elizabeth B. (Box 44)
  - Atwater, Frances A. (Box 44)
  - Avery, Grace A. (Box 44)
  - Bachmann, Edna G. (Box 44)
  - Bacon, Marjorie K. (Box 44)
  - Bailey, Dorothy V. (Box 44)
  - Blatchford, Barbara (Box 44)
  - Blakeslee, Gladys M. (Box 44)
  - Besser, Minna (Box 44)
  - Benedict, Hazle P. (Box 44)
  - Bender, Josephene (Box 44)
  - Bell, Constance (Box 44)
  - Beeken, Dorothy (Box 44)
  - Beardsley, Dorothy (Box 44)
  - Beard, Margaret K. (Box 44)
  - Beamensderfer, Eleanor (Box 44)
  - Baxter, Mildred F. (Box 44)
  - Barnes, Christine W. (Box 44)
  - Barcus, Katharine (Box 44)
  - Balmer, Catherine G. (Box 44)
  - Ball, Eunice W. (Box 44)
  - Boland, Margaret W. (Box 44)
  - Boniface, Symona F. (Box 44)
  - Bowen, Louise (Box 44)
  - Bowne, Helen L. (Box 44)
  - Brady, Mary B. (Box 44)
  - Brandeis, Leola (Box 44)
  - Brewster, Katrina M. (Box 44)
  - Briggs, Phebe (Box 44)
  - Brown, Georgie L. (Box 44)
  - Brown, Helen M. (Box 44)
  - Brown, Mary C. (Box 44)
  - Bull, Harriet F. (Box 44)
  - Burt, Irene E. (Box 44)
  - Bushman, Beatrice M. (Box 44)
  - Button, Leonora C. (Box 44)
  - Callow, Bessie R. (Box 44)
  - Canfield, Louise C. (Box 44)
  - Carlson, Esther F. (Box 44)
  - Carman, Gladys L. (Box 45)
  - Catlin, Marjorie A. (Box 45)
  - Cavert, Inez M. (Box 45)
  - Chandler, Helen W. (Box 45)
  - Chapman, Ella Louise (Box 45)
  - Clarke, Florence S. (Box 45)
  - Coe, Beatrice H. (Box 45)
  - Colding, Vera A. (Box 45)
  - Cole, Luella W. (Box 45)
  - Collins, Ruth M. (Box 45)
  - Comstock, Catherine S. (Box 45)
  - Congdon, Josephine (Box 45)
  - Conger, Wilhelmina DeP (Box 45)
  - Conwell, Mary (Box 45)
  - Cook, O Lucile (Box 45)
  - Core, Ruth K. (Box 45)
  - Cornwall, Ruth P. (Box 45)
  - Cosgrove, Elizabeth (Box 45)
  - Cox, Theodosia L. (Box 45)
  - Coye, Irene (Box 45)
  - Crandall, Dorothy D. (Box 45)
  - Crowell, Marion D. (Box 45)
  - Culbertson, Margaret L. (Box 45)
  - Cumming, Grace D. (Box 45)
  - Curtiss, Leah K. (Box 45)
  - Cushing, Leila H. (Box 45)
  - Davis, Dorothy H. (Box 45)
  - Downer, Emma (Box 45)
  - Drake, Leonore E. (Box 45)
  - Druien, Mildred M. (Box 45)
  - Duschak, Alice D. (Box 45)
  - Dutton, Edith H. (Box 45)
  - Edwards, Mabel E. (Box 45)
  - Emrich, Hilda W. (Box 45)
  - Enck, Edith N. (Box 45)
  - English, Katharine P. (Box 45)
  - Farnham, Gertrude P. (Box 45)
  - Farrier, Ednah C. (Box 45)
  - Finley, Ellen B. (Box 45)
  - Fite, Frances (Box 45)
  - Flick, Doris L. (Box 45)
  - Flickinger, Jean (Box 45)
  - Folks, Gertrude H. (Box 45)
  - Fowle, Priscilla H. (Box 45)
  - Gale, Esther H. (Box 45)
  - Galt, Priscilla M. (Box 45)
  - Gebhardt, Florence H. (Box 45)
  - Gilchrist, Elizabeth M. (Box 45)
  - Glover, Deborah N. (Box 45)
  - Goodrich, Caroline L. (Box 45)
  - Goss, Eleanor (Box 45)
  - Graham, Dorothy (Box 45)
  - Guckenberger, Dorothy S. (Box 45)
  - Hardin, Elizabeth A. (Box 45)
  - Harmstead, Charlotte L. (Box 45)
  - Harris, Rhoda E. (Box 45)
  - Hess, Louiseanna (Box 45)
  - Heath, Elizabeth M. (Box 45)
  - Hendrickson, Mary L. (Box 45)
  - Hertell, Helen D. (Box 45)
  - Hervey, Jane H. (Box 45)
  - Hewlett, Kathleen (Box 45)
  - Hickok, Jessie E. (Box 45)
  - Hoagland, Ruth A. (Box 45)
  - Hobbs, Eleanor M. (Box 45)
  - Hodge, Helen A. (Box 45)
  - Hoge, Dorcas O. (Box 45)
  - Hollinger, Anna M. (Box 45)
  - Holmes, Edith M. (Box 45)
  - Holstein, Abby V. (Box 45)
  - Holt, Eva M. (Box 45)
  - Holway, Lois L. (Box 45)
  - Homan, Lillie L. (Box 45)
  - Honywill, Mildred (Box 45)
  - Hopson, Lucile I. (Box 45)
  - Houghton, Dorothy (Box 45)
  - Howard, Emily (Box 45)
  - Howell, Annette (Box 45)
  - Hyde, Ruth (Box 45)
  - Jackman, Margaret (Box 45)
  - Jackson, Edith B. (Box 45)
  - Jeffris, Katharine L. (Box 45)
  - Jeffris, Ruth B. (Box 45)
  - Johnston, Elizabeth (Box 45)
  - Jonas, Isabel (Box 45)
  - Jones, Esther M. (Box 45)
  - Jones, Helen (Box 45)
  - Jones, Marjorie D. (Box 45)
  - Jones, Martha B. (Box 45)
  - Joseph, Alice M. (Box 45)
  - Joseph, Emma Eva (Box 45)
  - Keenan, Hetty B. (Box 45)
  - Keith, Annie H. (Box 45)
  - Keller, Elizabeth D. (Box 45)
  - Kellers, Irmarita (Box 45)
  - Kibbey, Gladys G. (Box 45)
  - Kirkus, Virginia (Box 45)
  - Knowles, Helen I. (Box 45)
  - Knowlton, Elizabeth (Box 45)
  - Lasalle, Amie T. (Box 45)
  - Law, Julia A. (Box 45)
  - Leitch, Norma P. (Box 45)
  - Leonori, Bessie F. (Box 45)
  - Leslie, Eleanor I. (Box 45)
  - Lewis, Clementine E. (Box 45)
  - Linder, Elizabeth S. (Box 46)
  - Locke, Helen (Box 46)
  - Lyman, Grace E. (Box 46)
  - Mabon, Janet P. (Box 46)
  - Mack, Edith F. (Box 46)
  - Macnicol, Laura E. (Box 46)
  - Marioneaux, Dorothy M. (Box 46)
  - Marsh, Marion (Box 46)
  - Marter, Gladys E. (Box 46)
  - McCreery, Elizabeth R. (Box 46)
  - McEvoy, Susan (Box 46)
  - McIlravy, Ruth A. (Box 46)
  - McKenna, Madeleine (Box 46)
  - McLean, Catherine (Box 46)
  - McManus, Mary B. (Box 46)
  - Messler, Mary J (Box 46)
  - Miller, Laura (Box 46)
  - Miller, Lucelia (Box 46)
  - Mills, L Hazelton (Box 46)
  - Molter, Ruth M. (Box 46)
  - Montague, Margaret (Box 46)
  - Moore, Barbara (Box 46)
  - Moore, Evangeline (Box 46)
  - Moore, F Aline (Box 46)
  - Moore, Helen B. (Box 46)
  - Mordorf, Dorothy A. (Box 46)
  - Mott, Margaret B. (Box 46)
  - Murray, Nereide J (Box 46)
  - Nason, Gertrude (Box 46)
  - Neare, Charlotte (Box 46)
  - Nichols, Grace A. (Box 46)
  - Nicholson, Agnes (Box 46)
  - Norton, Julia B. (Box 46)
  - Norton, Sarah L. (Box 46)
  - Noyes, Helen (Box 46)
  - Olds, Clara L. (Box 46)
  - Osborn, Laura (Box 46)
  - Paret, Marjorie (Box 46)
  - Pattison, Adele B. (Box 46)
  - Patton, Helen H. (Box 46)
  - Paul, Mary Jane (Box 46)
  - Peirce, Margaret W. (Box 46)
  - Peters, Florence (Box 46)
  - Phillips, Marguerita (Box 46)
  - Place, Katherine (Box 46)
  - Platt, Elizabeth A. (Box 46)
  - Preble, Barbara (Box 46)
  - Pringle, Bertha A. (Box 46)
  - Provoost, Charlotte M. (Box 46)
  - Ralli, Elaine P. (Box 46)
  - Rannells, Marion E. (Box 46)
  - Ransohoff, Esther (Box 46)
  - Raymer, Edith A. (Box 46)
  - Reichel, Madeline M. (Box 46)
  - Richardson, Mary S. (Box 46)
  - Ridgely, Philippa E. (Box 46)
  - Roach, Mary C. (Box 46)
  - Robbins, Marian (Box 46)
  - Rogers, Agnes (Box 46)
  - Rohn, Helen E. (Box 46)
  - Rose, Ethel L. (Box 46)
  - Rosenblatt, Amy B. (Box 46)
  - Rosewarne, Ruth (Box 46)
  - Rothschild, Edith L. (Box 46)
  - Sagendorph, Dorothy J (Box 46)
  - Schmidt, Katherine M. (Box 46)
  - Schumacher, Catherine H. (Box 46)
  - Scott, Katherine R. (Box 46)
  - Seasholes, Amy L. (Box 46)
  - Service, Helen F. (Box 46)
  - Seymour, Alma B. (Box 46)
  - Sharpe, Rosa D. (Box 46)
  - Shaw, Helen C. (Box 46)
  - Showalter, Lucile M. (Box 46)
  - Sisson, Mildred H. (Box 46)
  - Sleght, Mabel L. (Box 46)
  - Smith, Eloessa (Box 46)
  - Smith, Frances D. (Box 46)
  - Smart, Sara (Box 46)
  - Spicer, Gladys (Box 46)
  - Stabler, Dorothy (Box 46)
  - Stephens, Ruth I. (Box 46)
  - Stimson, Anna K. (Box 46)
  - Stout, Alice L. (Box 46)
  - Strait, Helen E. (Box 46)
  - Strait, Martha E. (Box 46)
  - Strasburg, Hermine A. (Box 46)
  - Strelitz, Dorothy M. (Box 46)
  - Strunz, Eda A. (Box 46)
  - Stuart, Margaret H. (Box 46)
  - Swinton, Roberta B. (Box 46)
  - Taggart, Mabel C. (Box 46)
  - Tawney, Helen (Box 46)
  - Taylor, Eleanor B. (Box 46)
  - Taylor, Eloise (Box 46)
  - Taylor, Ruth M. (Box 46)
  - Tebo, Mabel K. (Box 46)
  - Thomas, Cyra (Box 46)
  - Tillotson, Abby B. (Box 46)
  - Tillotson, Lucy A. (Box 46)
  - Tindle, Harriet M. (Box 46)
  - Tinley, Gertrude M. (Box 46)
  - Tompkins, Eleanor M. (Box 46)
  - Trager, Elma H. (Box 46)
  - Trevor, Margaret (Box 46)
  - Ullrich, Janet R. (Box 46)
  - Underhill, Editha (Box 46)
  - Van Allen, Martha M. (Box 46)
  - Van Arsdale, A Maude (Box 46)
  - Van Dusen, Katharine P. (Box 47)
  - Van Evera, Grace R. (Box 47)
  - Vollrath, Mildred D. (Box 47)
  - Vose, Margaret B. (Box 47)
  - Wadsworth, Isabella (Box 47)
  - Wagner, Miriam E. (Box 47)
  - Walker, Amelia (Box 47)
  - Walker, Ruth (Box 47)
  - Wallace, Margaret (Box 47)
  - Wardwell, Margaret (Box 47)
  - Watson, Grace M. (Box 47)
  - Watson, Miriam (Box 47)
  - Weil, Florine R. (Box 47)
  - Welch, Florence M. (Box 47)
  - Wells, Elizabeth (Box 47)
  - Wells, Mary (Box 47)
  - West, Alice M. (Box 47)
  - West, Helen T. (Box 47)
  - Whipple, Helen K. (Box 47)
  - White, Jessie D. (Box 47)
  - White, Martha I. (Box 47)
  - Whiting, Anne H. (Box 47)
  - Wickham, Evelyn W. (Box 47)
  - Wright, Elizabeth Von B. (Box 47)
  - Wilklow, Ethel C. (Box 47)
  - Williams, Barbara (Box 47)
  - Williams, Lois P. (Box 47)
  - Williamson, Mildred B. (Box 47)
  - Winestine, Frederica (Box 47)
  - Wishart, Laura B. (Box 47)
  - Wood, Frances (Box 47)
  - Woodbury, Helen (Box 47)
  - Woodruff, Sylvia W. (Box 47)
  - Woolsey, Marjorie E. (Box 47)
  - Woolverton, Dorothy (Box 47)
  - Worsham, Josephine (Box 47)
  - Yager, Diana L. (Box 47)
  - Yamada, Koto (Box 47)
  - Zimmers, Phyllis (Box 47)
- Class of 1917
  - Addington, Anna C. (Box 47)
  - Allyn, Donna B. (Box 47)
  - Almy, Ann C. (Box 47)
  - Anthony, Constance E. (Box 47)
  - Archibold, Virginia (Box 47)
  - Armitage, F Marion (Box 47)
  - Arnold, Nathalie F. (Box 47)
  - Arthur, Sarah T. (Box 47)
  - Babbott, Lydia P. (Box 47)
  - Babcock, Charlotte N. (Box 47)
  - Bacon, Caroline W. (Box 47)
  - Barbour, Myra S. (Box 47)
  - Barr, Florence K. (Box 47)
  - Bartow, Charlotte W. (Box 47)
  - Benedict, Madeline (Box 47)
  - Beymer, Rachel E. (Box 47)
  - Bird, Elisabeth W. (Box 47)
  - Borland, Elizabeth V. (Box 47)
  - Brightbill, Helen E. (Box 47)
  - Brinsmade, Abigail I. (Box 47)
  - Bristol, Elisabeth (Box 47)
  - Broderick, Helen G. (Box 47)
  - Broomall, Carlota (Box 47)
  - Brown, Dorothy W. (Box 47)
  - Brown, Elizabeth A. (Box 47)
  - Brown, Mary (Box 47)
  - Brown, Mary K. (Box 47)
  - Brown, Vivian J (Box 47)
  - Bryant, Julia C. (Box 47)
  - Buck, Flora (Box 47)
  - Buffum, Margaret (Box 47)
  - Bullard, Doris B. (Box 47)
  - Burke, Olive (Box 47)
  - Burwell, Virginia K. (Box 47)
  - Bushman, Evelyn (Box 47)
  - Buttrick, Caroline I. (Box 47)
  - Campbell, Adele (Box 47)
  - Campbell, Alice M. (Box 47)
  - Campbell, Dorothea L. (Box 47)
  - Capen, Lila (Box 47)
  - Carbaugh, Phyllis M. (Box 47)
  - Carden, Mae (Box 47)
  - Carter, Dorothy J (Box 47)
  - Carter, Helen J (Box 47)
  - Cattell, Judith H. (Box 47)
  - Cheney, Frances G. (Box 47)
  - Clark, Jeanette O. (Box 47)
  - Cobb, Janet I. (Box 47)
  - Cobb, Margaret E. (Box 47)
  - Colton, Suzanne B. (Box 47)
  - Congdon, Elisabeth M. (Box 47)
  - Conger, Esther S. (Box 47)
  - Cook, Mildred E. (Box 47)
  - Coonley, Lydia A. (Box 47)
  - Copenhaver, Dorothy E. (Box 47)
  - Cornell, Dorothy (Box 47)
  - Cornell, Grace H. (Box 47)
  - Cox, Gladys A. (Box 47)
  - Crabbe, Elizabeth R. (Box 47)
  - Crothers, Helen M. (Box 47)
  - Crowley, Dorothy E. (Box 47)
  - Culver, Mary (Box 47)
  - Cummings, Eloise Hood (Box 47)
  - Curtis, Katharine H. (Box 47)
  - Danforth, Dorothy (Box 47)
  - Davis, Helen Arthur (Box 47)
  - Decker, Helen V. (Box 48)
  - Delapena, Ruth (Box 48)
  - Dennis, Mildred B. (Box 48)
  - Doherty, Cornelia B. (Box 48)
  - Donaghue, Ethel F. (Box 48)
  - Drumer, Doris E. (Box 48)
  - Dumond, Helen M. (Box 48)
  - Dunmire, Ethel m (Box 48)
  - Eaton, Mary L. (Box 48)
  - Edwards, Dorothy (Box 48)
  - Einstein, Jeanette R. (Box 48)
  - Ellsworth, J Josephine (Box 48)
  - Evarts, Helen W. (Box 48)
  - Farish, Frances M. (Box 48)
  - Farley, Margaret (Box 48)
  - Farr, Helen A. (Box 48)
  - Farrall, Ruth T. (Box 48)
  - Fenstermaker, Mary I. (Box 48)
  - Ferree, Marian R. (Box 48)
  - Filene, Catherine (Box 48)
  - Finck, Margaret (Box 48)
  - Forman, Isabel R. (Box 48)
  - Foster, Miriam (Box 48)
  - Fox, Mary M. (Box 48)
  - Fraser, Frances M. (Box 48)
  - Gallagher, S Margaret (Box 48)
  - Gardner, Anne W. (Box 48)
  - Garver, Frances N. (Box 48)
  - Glascock, Josephine R. (Box 48)
  - Goes, Bertha L. (Box 48)
  - Goodnow, Anne H. (Box 48)
  - Gouinlock, Dorothy M. (Box 48)
  - Graham, Margaret D. (Box 48)
  - Granger, Althea J (Box 48)
  - Graves, Katharine B. (Box 48)
  - Gray, Lillian S. (Box 48)
  - Gregory, Marie L. (Box 48)
  - Gunz, Helen M. (Box 48)
  - Guy, Mary B. (Box 48)
  - Hackney, Marguerite (Box 48)
  - Hadley, Grace M. (Box 48)
  - Haff, Gertrude B. (Box 48)
  - Hand, Dorothy (Box 48)
  - Hartshorne, Frances (Box 48)
  - Hasler, Bertha W. (Box 48)
  - Hatch, Adeline L. (Box 48)
  - Hathaway, Lillie V. (Box 48)
  - Heath, Evelyn A. (Box 48)
  - Heaton, Elizabeth H. (Box 48)
  - Hert, Mildred H. (Box 48)
  - Hincks, Elizabeth M. (Box 48)
  - Hiteman, Isa M. (Box 48)
  - Holbrook, Carolyn (Box 48)
  - Holloway, Roberta (Box 48)
  - Hopkins, Alice W. (Box 48)
  - Hornby, Alice W. (Box 48)
  - Horne, Mary (Box 48)
  - Horne, Mary S. (Box 48)
  - Houston, Harriette E. (Box 48)
  - Howe, Susanne (Box 48)
  - Hubbell, Helen C. (Box 48)
  - Hunt, Madeleine (Box 48)
  - Huntington, Constance (Box 48)
  - Hussey, Eleanor (Box 48)
  - Hyde, Grace (Box 48)
  - Ickler, Caroline S. (Box 48)
  - Irving, Beatrice S. (Box 48)
  - Iszard, Muriel E. (Box 48)
  - Jadwin, Charlotte F. (Box 48)
  - Jaggard, Katrina (Box 48)
  - Jenison, Monell (Box 48)
  - Jones, Hester (Box 48)
  - Kennedy, Helen J (Box 48)
  - Kennedy, Margaret V. (Box 48)
  - Kincaid, Margaret (Box 48)
  - Kindred, Gladys M. (Box 48)
  - Kinsley, Evelyn (Box 48)
  - Knapp, Esther (Box 48)
  - Krause, Dorothy J (Box 48)
  - Krick, E Kathryn (Box 48)
  - Kruse, Elisabeth D. (Box 48)
  - Lamprecht, Elizabeth (Box 48)
  - Landon, Elizabeth A. (Box 48)
  - Lane, Aline (Box 48)
  - Lapham, Olive M. (Box 48)
  - Leary Marian E. (Box 48)
  - Lederman, Minna (Box 48)
  - Lee, Virginia (Box 48)
  - Leicht, Gretchen (Box 48)
  - Leonard, Ruth F. (Box 48)
  - Lindau, Ruth V. (Box 48)
  - Lyday, June (Box 48)
  - MacHado, Eleanor W. (Box 48)
  - Maher, Mary D. (Box 48)
  - Mahoney, M Madeline (Box 48)
  - Malevinsky, Dorothy (Box 48)
  - Mandell, Sibyl (Box 48)
  - Marrett, Hilda (Box 48)
  - Marshall, Philena (Box 48)
  - Martin, Helen P. (Box 48)
  - Mason, Eugenia C. (Box 48)
  - Maycock, Hannah P. (Box 48)
  - Maynard, Frieda B. (Box 48)
  - McAfee, Katharine (Box 48)
  - McCarthy, Elizabeth (Box 48)
  - McDowell, Laura E. (Box 48)
  - McEldowney, Annabel (Box 48)
  - McGraw, Marguerite K. (Box 48)
  - McIlravy, Alice P. (Box 48)
  - McIntosh, Marjorie (Box 48)
  - Mendelson, Anna W. (Box 48)
  - Merchant, Clara (Box 48)
  - Merrell, Elinor (Box 48)
  - Merz, Lucy A. (Box 48)
  - Metzgar, Thelma F. (Box 48)
  - Millay, Edna St V. (Box 49)
  - Miller, Jeannette C. (Box 49)
  - Miller, Lilian M. (Box 49)
  - Miller, Marjorie E. (Box 49)
  - Mills, Elizabeth S. (Box 49)
  - Mollart, Gladys (Box 49)
  - Moore, Anna C. (Box 49)
  - Moore, Helen R. (Box 49)
  - Morris, Margaret L. (Box 49)
  - Nason, Edith H. (Box 49)
  - Neff, Clarine (Box 49)
  - Newton, Elizabeth M. (Box 49)
  - Nichols, Florence E. (Box 49)
  - Nickerson, Marjorie G. (Box 49)
  - Niles, Jessie E. (Box 49)
  - Nourse, Ella F. (Box 49)
  - Olmstead, Anna E. (Box 49)
  - Osborn, Lucretia M. (Box 49)
  - Owens, Horatia (Box 49)
  - Palmer, Josephine L. (Box 49)
  - Parker, Edna A. (Box 49)
  - Parker, Julia A. (Box 49)
  - Parsons, Elizabeth I. (Box 49)
  - Patten, Eugenia (Box 49)
  - Peck, Marjorie (Box 49)
  - Peck, Mary M. (Box 49)
  - Perry, Dorothy Hills (Box 49)
  - Pickering, Roberta H. (Box 49)
  - Pickslay, Dorothy D. (Box 49)
  - Pond, Inez M. (Box 49)
  - Pope, Mary L. (Box 49)
  - Potter, Helen H. (Box 49)
  - Pratt, Gertrude L. (Box 49)
  - Putnam, Elizabeth W. (Box 49)
  - Pyle, Eleanor (Box 49)
  - Reed, Katherine I. (Box 49)
  - Remington, Katherine (Box 49)
  - Richardson, Hattie E. (Box 49)
  - Robinson, Martha (Box 49)
  - Roper, Grace H. (Box 49)
  - Sague, Isobel (Box 49)
  - Sailer, Josephine (Box 49)
  - Salladin, Margaret L. (Box 49)
  - Satterthwait, Alice (Box 49)
  - Sawtell, Ruth O. (Box 49)
  - Scheiblich, Elizabeth J (Box 49)
  - Scheuer, Bianca L. (Box 49)
  - Scholton, Helen A. (Box 49)
  - Scull, Anna C. (Box 49)
  - Slingerland, M Charlotte (Box 49)
  - Sloane, M Marion (Box 49)
  - Smart, F Marie (Box 49)
  - Smith, Agnes H. (Box 49)
  - Smith, Annie P. (Box 49)
  - Smith, Dorothy J (Box 49)
  - Smith, Edith T. (Box 49)
  - Smith, Hester (Box 49)
  - Smith, Lucy D. (Box 49)
  - Spur, Jean W. (Box 49)
  - Stafford, Elizabeth (Box 49)
  - Steele, Margaret E. (Box 49)
  - Stevens, Letha L. (Box 49)
  - Stilson, Laura F. (Box 49)
  - Stout, Frances B. (Box 49)
  - Strahan, Julia H. (Box 49)
  - Stratton, Helen E. (Box 49)
  - Strawbridge, Marguerite (Box 49)
  - Streng, Rebekah R. (Box 49)
  - Stuckslager, Mary C. (Box 49)
  - Swann, Anne P. (Box 49)
  - Swetland, Dorothy A. (Box 49)
  - Swift, Louise F. (Box 49)
  - Talmage, Gertrude D. (Box 49)
  - Talmage, Susan (Box 49)
  - Tangeman, Margaret L. (Box 49)
  - Taylor, Grace K. (Box 49)
  - Thompson, Mildred (Box 49)
  - Thorburn, Helen C. (Box 49)
  - Thorp, Anne L. (Box 49)
  - Thrasher, Corinne (Box 49)
  - Tilt, Katharine B. (Box 49)
  - Twaddell, Louise P. (Box 49)
  - Tyler, Grace K. (Box 49)
  - Van De Water, Charlotte (Box 49)
  - Vanden Bosch, Wilhelmina L. (Box 49)
  - Vogel, Margaret G. (Box 49)
  - Wagner, Dorothea (Box 49)
  - Walker, F Ruth (Box 49)